

Marc Leerink

Software Engineering Student

Berlin, Germany 015901976176 · maleerink@gmail.com

Heads Radio, ELEVE,
Discogs, Leerinc

Skills

Creativity & Problem Solving Communication
Conceptual Thinking

English German Dutch

Hobbies

Programming, collecting records, playing didgeridoo,

Profile

Hi! I am Marc Leerink, a passionate music lover from the Netherlands living in Berlin. I am a software engineering student at CODE University. My main interests are sound and technology and I am always looking for ways to combine the two. I have over 4 years experience in organizing music events and managing an music radio whilst producing and DJing on the side as well as advising clients in healthcare. My character would be best described as curious, communicative and creative. Furthermore, I possess strong conceptual thinking skills and work solution-oriented with high attention to detail.

Employment History

Radio manager/technician, Sameheads, Berlin

August 2019 — Present

<u>Heads Radio</u> is the radio station from <u>Sameheads</u>. I have set up the station from scratch. My main responsibilities include: Setting up the server for live streaming on different platforms, (online) promotion on different platforms, archiving shows on different platforms and curating the music program including artist handling.

Event Promoter, ELEVE, Berlin

September 2017 - Present

Co-owner of <u>ELEVE</u>, a platform in Berlin that focuses on giving emerging anti-pop artists a stage. We did events at <u>Sameheads</u> and <u>Arkaoda</u>. I am responsible for the bookings, artist handling and (online) promotion.

DJ/Producer/Collector, Leerinc, Berlin

January 2016 — Present

Producing and DJ'ing as <u>Leerinc</u> at music events in Berlin and Amsterdam. I have played at clubs such as <u>Radion</u> and <u>Sameheads</u> and did various radio shows at <u>Redlight Radio</u> and <u>LYL</u> to name a few. In my music I like to experiment and show different sides of myself. This translates into my diverse taste as a record <u>collector</u> as well. I also hosts <u>Multidentity</u> on <u>Noods Radio</u>, which is a self organizing mix series with a self choosing chain of artists.

Physiotherapist, Therapiezentrum Siegfriedshofe, Berlin

May 2018 — May 2020

Successfully diagnosing patients prior to designing and executing an effective treatment plan, motivating patients with various proven communication techniques including motivational interviewing, working together with other medical personnel to provide the best care possible as well as maintaining accurate and organized patient documentation in various programs including <a href="https://documentation.org/rep-eff-to-the-best-to-the-b

Customer Care Specialist/Design Specialist, Vistaprint, Berlin

October 2017 - April 2018

Handling customer inquiries with a high customer satisfaction rate, providing tailored guidance to customers on their design of various printed products as well as providing marketing advice specific to their business.

Education

Bachelor of Science: Physiotherapy, Amsterdam University Of Applied Sience, Amsterdam

September 2011 — June 2016

Bernard Lievegoed College for Liberal Arts, Driebergen-Zeist September 2010 — July 2011

Bachelor of Science: Software Engineering, CODE University, Berlin July 2021 — August 2024

References

References available upon request